usedcarexpert.co.uk 2011-12-21

# Used Car Expert Disclaimer

ALL AGREEMENTS WITH USED CAR EXPERT ARE SUBJECT TO THE LAWS OF ENGLAND & WALES

Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using this website (the Site ). Using this Site indicates that you accept these terms and conditions. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, do not use this Site.

We may change our terms and conditions from time to time so you should review them regularly. Your use of this Site will be deemed an acceptance of the terms and conditions existing at that time.

**Terms and conditions**

**1. About us**

1.1 the Site is operated by a Limited company, SDO Media, registered in England, trading as Used Car Expert, from 12 Melcombe Place, London, NW1 6JJ.

**2.   Accessing This Site**  
2.1. We reserve the right to withdraw or amend the services we provide on this Site without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason this Site is unavailable at any time or for any period.   
2.2. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of this Site, or this entire Site, to users who have registered with us.  
2.3. If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any third party. We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms and conditions.

**3\. Permitted Use**  
3.1. Subject to clause 3.2, you may print and download extracts from this Site for non-commercial use on the following basis:   
3.1.1. no documents or related graphics on the Site are modified in any way;  
3.1.2. no graphics on the Site are used separately from accompanying text;  
and  
3.1.3. no copyright and trade mark notices are removed.   
3.2. You agree not to:   
3.2.1. use any part of the materials on this Site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors;   
3.2.2. copy, reproduce, distribute, republish, download, display, post or transmit in any form or by any means any content of this Site, except as permitted above;   

**4\. Intellectual Property Rights**  
4.1. Unless otherwise specified, we are the owner or licensee of all intellectual property rights in the Site, and in the material published on it. Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved.   
4.2. Unless otherwise specified, the authors of the literary and artistic works in the materials contained in the Site have asserted their moral right pursuant to Section 77 of the Copyright Designs and Patents Act 1988 to be identified as the author of those works.

**5\. Reliance On Information Posted**  
5.1. The information contained in the material on this Site is for information purposes only and does not constitute advice. We therefore disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by any user of this Site, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.   
5.2. Subject to clause 5.3 and to the extent permitted by law, we hereby expressly exclude:   
5.2.1. all conditions, warranties and other terms which might otherwise be implied by statute, common law or the law of equity;   
5.2.2. any liability for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by any user in connection with use of this Site, including without limitation any liability for:   
5.2.2.1. loss of income or revenue;  
5.2.2.2. loss of business;   
5.2.2.3. loss of profits or contracts;   
5.2.2.4. loss of anticipated savings;   
5.2.2.5. loss of data;  
5.2.2.6. loss of goodwill;   
5.2.2.7. wasted management or office time; and for any other loss or damage of any kind, however arising whether caused by tort (including negligence), breach of contract or otherwise, even if foreseeable.  
5.3. We do not exclude liability for death or personal injury arising from our negligence nor any other liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.

**6\. Third Party Material**   
This Site may contain material submitted and created by third parties including other Site users. We exclude all liability for any illegality arising from or error, omission or inaccuracy in such material and we take no responsibility for such material.

**7\. Links From This Site**  
Where this Site contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them except as may be required by law.

**8\. Material Submitted By You  
**8.1. By submitting any material to us, you :   
8.1.1. automatically grant us a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable licence to use, reproduce, modify, edit, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display such material (in whole or part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in such content; and  
8.1.2. waive all your moral rights in such materials.  
8.2. You acknowledge that we are not obliged to publish any material submitted by you.   
8.3. You agree not to post any material:   
8.3.1. that is threatening, defamatory, offensive, abusive, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory, blasphemous, pornographic, in breach of confidence, in breach of privacy; or  
8.3.2. for which you have not obtained all necessary licences and/or approvals; or  
8.3.3. which constitutes or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise be contrary to the law of or infringe the rights of any third party, in the UK; or   
8.3.4. which is technically harmful (including, without limitation, computer viruses, logic bombs, Trojan horses, worms, harmful components, corrupted data or other malicious software or harmful data).   
8.4. We will fully co-operate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or locate anyone posting material in breach of clause 8.3.

**9\. Data Protection and Privacy  
**9.1. We process information about you in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you consent to such processing and you warrant to the best of your knowledge and belief that all data provided by you is accurate.   
9.2. We hold a data protection registration and comply with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**10\. Validity  
**

If any term, condition, or provision of these terms and conditions is determined to be unlawful, invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, the validity and enforceability of the remaining terms, conditions and provisions shall not in any way be affected or impaired thereby.

**11\. Entire Agreement  
**

These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and us relating to the subject matter herein.

**12\. Jurisdiction and Applicable Law  
**

The English courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising from, or related to, this Site. These terms and conditions are governed by English Law. 

**Advertising disclaimer**

All advertisements on this Site are published in good faith.  The Site does not, under any circumstances, accept responsibility for the accuracy or otherwise of any advertisement found on the Site, nor is any kind of warranty expressed or implied by such publication

**Technical checks disclaimer**

The use of the Site, guides, products and any other services offered by the Site are intended only as a guide to assessing the quality of used cars. 

Only a qualified mechanic can definitely assess the condition of a vehicle . The site, draws specific attention to the inherent danger associated with mechanical vehicles and carrying out checks upon them.

If in any doubt as to how safe a test may be, the user should consult a qualified mechanic. Users are reminded that vehicles have both moving parts and associated heat when in operation and appropriate caution must be exercised.

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies only to this website (the Site) If you do not accept this privacy policy, you should not use this Site.

****Collection Of Personal Information****

The Site collects personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) when you complete registration or enquiry forms or send emails to us. Please do not submit your personal information to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

****Collection Of Other Information****

In addition to personal information, we may collect information about you automatically when you visit the Site. The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor visitors to the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by your web browser when you first visit the Site. The cookie allows us to identify your computer and find out details about your last visit. Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience with the Site will be as quick or responsive as if you do receive cookies.

The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not personally identifiable, it includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the internet e.g. operating system and platform, IP addrss, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on the Site and your geographical location. **  
 **

****Use Of Your Information****

By using this Site, you agree that the Site may collect, hold, process and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with the Site services. These include (without limitation):

****Sharing Your Information****

By using the Site, you agree that we may disclose your personal informat ion to any company that is a contracted supplier to the Site where it is required to deliver a service you have requested including but not limited to car data checks, insurance and financial services, advertising display, car brochures, car test drives, car sales. Subject to our obtaining your express consent, we may also supply personal information about you to other third parties. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to comply with applicable laws and government or regulatory bodies lawful requests for information. We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business. Furthermore, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (which may not provide the same protection for such information as the United Kingdom provides) in the event that the processing of your information involves such a transfer.

****Safeguards And Security****

No data transmission over the internet can be entirely secure, so we do not guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of the Site. However, we use reasonable endeavors to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorised access or use by using encryption technology. In addition to these safeguards, your personal information is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act 1998. This provides that the information which we hold about you should be processed fairly and lawfully, should be accurate, relevant and not excessive, not be retained for longer than is necessary and, if applicable, be kept up to date. For more information on the Data Protection Act 1998 and your related rights please see www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk 

****Accessing Your Information****

****If you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hld about you, or have any other queries please write to us (including full details of your request) at:****

****SDO Media****

****12 Melcombe Place****

****London****

****NW1 6JJ****

****We may charge a small administration fee in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.****

Advertisements on our site are provided by another organisation. Our advertising partner will serve ads that it believes are most likely to be of interest to you, based on information about your visit to this and other websites (this information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number). In order to do this, our advertising partner may need to place a cookie (a small text file) on your computer. For more information about this type of online behavioural advertising, about cookies, and about how to turn this feature off, please visit http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk.
